当我们共舞时*
*When we dance together
我的世界变得虚幻*
*My world's in disguise
犹如童话*
*It's a fairyland tale
终于成真*
*That's come true
你看着我*
*And when you look at me
眸中有星空*
*With those stars in your eyes
我愿与你跳着华尔兹穿越德州*
*I could waltz across Texas with you
跳着华尔兹穿越德州*
*Waltz across Texas
怀里抱着你*
*With you in my arms
抱歉出了点小问题  马上就能修好
Sorry about the hiccup, folks. It won't be long.
和你跳着华尔兹穿越德州*
*Waltz across Texas with you
像童话里的结局*
*Like a storybook ending
我被你深深吸引*
*I'm lost in your charms
给你五分钟
You got five minutes.
我愿与你跳着华尔兹穿越德州*
*And I could waltz across Texas with you
大家好啊
Howdy, folks.
请问阿尔玛·梅·厄尔巴诺女士在车上吗
Could someone tell me if Mrs. Alma May Urbano is on board?
阿尔玛·梅·厄尔巴诺
Alma May Urbano.
你在这儿  你好亲爱的
There you are. Hello, dear.
真高兴认识你
Very good to meet you.
我叫吉米
My name's Jimmy.
之前在矶鹞渡时我想拜访你
I tried to visit you at Sandpiper,
但他们不让  你知道吗
but they wouldn't allow me to. Hey, you know what?
那也没关系
It doesn't matter.
我看见车坏了  你正好在车里
I saw your bus broken down, here you are.
我真幸运
Lucky me.
你希望我称呼你厄尔巴诺女士
Do you prefer to be called Mrs. Urbano
阿尔玛·梅  还是只叫阿尔玛就好
or Alma May or just plain Alma?
我姓麦吉尔  但叫我吉米就好
My last name is McGill, but you can call me Jimmy.
大家好  我叫吉米·麦吉尔
Hey, everyone! My name's Jimmy McGill.
我是名律师  但别在意我
I'm an attorney at law, but, uh, don't mind me.
你们继续聊天吧
Just talk amongst yourselves.
阿尔玛·梅
Now, Alma May,
你还记得回复过我律所寄来的信函吗
do you recall responding to a mailer from my law firm,
新墨西哥州圣达菲的戴维斯梅因律所
Davis & Main, of Santa Fe, New Mexico?
我记不住了
I...I don't know.
我们想帮助那些
Well, we were looking to help any Sandpiper residents
因基础商品和服务
who may have been overcharged
可能被超额收费的矶鹞渡居民
for, uh, basic goods and services.
这下能想起来了吧
Now, does that ring a bell?
可能吧  是黄色的信封吗
Maybe. Was it yellow?
是浅黄色的
It's canary yellow.
我亲自选的颜色
I picked that color myself.
女士  我来这儿是为了确保你能拿回那笔钱
Well, ma'am, I'm here to make sure you get your money back.
你们在说什么
What are you talking about?
谁抢走了阿尔玛·梅的钱
Who took Alma May's money?
这个问题问得好
Uh, well, now, that's a very good question.
感谢你的提问  你是
And thank you for asking, mister, uh...?
艾莫斯  艾莫斯·莱德克
Amos -- Amos Lydecker.
莱德克先生  我是吉米·麦吉尔
Mr. Lydecker, Jimmy McGill.
其实不是谁抢走了谁的钱
Now, nobody took anybody's money, uh, exactly.
明白吗
Okay?
不是矶鹞渡的人
It's not like the Sandpiper people, you know,
戴上滑雪面罩
put on a ski mask and, uh...
持枪打劫了阿尔玛·梅
mugged Alma May here at gunpoint.
你们别在脑中想象这种场面
So I want you to put that mental image right out of your head.
我们现在说的更像是一种
See, what we're talking about here is more of a --
一点小矛盾
it's just a discrepancy.
一件小事而已
It's -- it's a little thing.
没什么恶意
It's -- it's fairly innocent.
但我们得解决
But we need to fix it.
明白吗
Do you follow me?
这么说吧
Well, put it this way.
阿尔玛·梅  假设说你和你男朋友
Alma May, let's say you're out on a date
出门约会
with your boyfriend.
你有男朋友  是吧
You do have a boyfriend, right?
没有吗
You don't?
拜托  你
Come on. You --
阿尔玛·梅瞒着我
Alma May's holding out on me.
你有侄子吗
Do you have a nephew?
侄子吗  有  他叫史蒂夫
Nephew? Oh, y-yes -- Steve.
好  史蒂夫
Okay, Steve.
他是个好人吗
Is he a good guy?
他非常好
Yeah, very good.
好
Okay.
假设说你和史蒂夫
So, let's say you and Steve go out to dinner
去博蒂餐厅吃饭
at, uh... well, Birdie's.
-你们今天都要去那儿  是吧  -对
- That's where you're all headed today, right? - Right.
好
All right.
你们俩享受了一顿大餐
So, both of you have a great meal.
你们吃了软炸牛排配青豆
It's chicken-fried steak and green beans,
一切都非常完美
and it's all perfect.
该结账了
Here comes the check.
"等一下
"Hey, wait a doggone --
"一块奶酪饼干竟然要二十四块钱
24 bucks for a side of buttermilk biscuits?
"这可不太对劲  是吧"
That doesn't sound right, now, does it?"
当然不对
No, it does not.
似乎是算错了
It sounds like something got added up wrong.
你当然要派你侄子史蒂夫去和经理谈谈
Well, naturally, you send your nephew Steve to talk to the manager,
经理当然也改正了错误
and naturally, the manager corrects the mistake.
而且  他还送给你一张
And what's more, he gives you a coupon
下次免费吃饭的优惠券
for a free meal next time you come in.
这听起来怎么样
How about that?
很好
Good.
如今  矶鹞渡也是这么一回事
Well, same kind of thing is what happened at Sandpiper Crossing.
最令我心痛的莫过于
And nothing makes me sadder
眼见美国最伟大的一代
than to see people of the Greatest Generation --
经历了经济大萧条  参与了二战的一代
我自己爷爷奶奶那一代
people like my own Nana and Bobo --
被一些大公司敲竹杠
gettin' overcharged by some great, big company --
就算那纯属意外
even if it was an accident.
我知道矶鹞渡的好伙计们
Now, I know that the good people at Sandpiper
迟早都会改正错误  但你知道吗
want to make this right sooner or later, but you know what?
有时候呢  把这事交给侄子史蒂夫
Well, sometimes, it's just easier if you get your nephew Steve
你会更轻松
to go take care of it for you.
而你可以把我当成他
And that's how I want you to think of me.
乔治亚娜
Georgiana.
乔治妹妹  谢谢你
Hey, there, Georgie girl. Thank you.
我需要的都在这儿了
Oh, it's all there, everything I need.
非常感谢你们  好好享用午餐
Thank you so much. Enjoy your lunch.
阿尔玛·梅  真棒
Alma May, you did it.
谢谢你  谢谢你
Thank you so much. Thank you.
谢谢  亨利
Thank you, Henry.
博蒂餐厅
很好
All right.
苏  很好
Hey, Sue. Okay.
优美的字迹
Beautiful penmanship.
失传的艺术
A lost art.
绝命律师
第二季 第三集
斯韦卡特和考科利正考虑主动出击
Schweikart and Cokely are pursuing an aggressive strategy,
但参考相关判例法
but looking at the relevant case law,
我认为这位地方法官不会吃这一套
I don't think it's going to play with this magistrate judge.
我研读了她许多过去的判决
I read over a dozen of her rulings,
所有类似案件中  她都站在原告这一方
all of which have sided with the plaintiff on cases like this.
我已将此作为备忘附在今天的资料里
I've included a memo to that effect in today's materials,
供各位空暇时细读
which you can peruse at your leisure.
谢谢  艾琳
Thanks, Erin.
我们接着讨论客户联系事宜吧
How about we move on to client outreach?
吉米
Jimmy?
你在听吗
You still with us?
我来说吧  免得你自夸
I'm gonna save you from having to brag.
过去三周内有超过两百位矶鹞渡新委托人签字
Over 200 new Sandpiper clients signed over the past three weeks.
做得好  吉米
Well-done, Jimmy.
谢谢你  谢谢  克利福德
Thank you. Thanks, Cliff.
目前
Uh, right now,
我们正在整个西南地区寻找委托人
we're in the process of mapping out the entire southwest,
优先锁定几家最大的矶鹞渡机构
targeting the largest Sandpiper facilities first.
凤凰城  科泉市  沃思堡  普罗沃
Phoenix, Colorado Springs, Fort Worth, Provo --
这还只是第一步
that's just for starters.
我的理想目标是  月底前再签下两百人
Ideally, my goal -- another 200 by the end of the month.
有了这么多人  我们有很大机会
With this many folks, we have an excellent shot
在各区的集体诉讼中
at a solid batch of plaintiffs
积累足够的原告人数
for the classes in each district.
非常好
Excellent.
期待你下一次汇报
Look forward to the next report.
接着是更棘手的议题  协调诉讼
On to a stickier wicket -- coordinating actions.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
继续讨论之前
Before we move on,
我想再花点时间谈谈客户联系
I'd like to go back to client outreach just for a moment.
看到这些数据
Looking over these numbers here,
成果真是惊人  吉米
really, astonishing results, Jimmy.
真了不起
Incredible.
你这一趟阿马里洛之行
Your last trip to Amarillo,
带回了二十二个新委托人
you came back with 22 new clients.
-是二十四  -二十四
- 24. - 24.
我有点疑惑
I'm confused.
总共有多少人回复了我们的直达信函
Um, how many people out there actually responded to our direct mailer?
一个
One.
是的  好的
Oh. Right. Yeah.
阿尔玛·梅·厄尔巴诺太太
A Mrs. Alma May Urbano.
但你从一个回复里又搞定了二十四位新委托人
But you got 24 new clients from this one response?
这真是...
That is -- Wow.
过奖了
Well, you're welcome.
怎么  难道有问题吗
I mean, what? Is there a problem?
这难免会让某些人
Well, uh, might not some parties --
比方说  辩护方
the opposing counsel, for example --
发现这差异  因此认为
see this differential and conclude
这其中可能存在教唆之嫌
that there may have been some solicitation involved?
我没有教唆他们
I did not solicit.
我只想知道你如何解释你的成功
I'm just wondering how you account for your success.
因为这必定会引起
Because it will definitely raise eyebrows
斯韦卡特和考科利的质疑
over at Schweikart & Cokely.
抱歉但这是事实
I'm sorry, but it will.
特别是牵涉到老年人的案子
Particularly in a case involving seniors,
美国律师协会有关教唆的职业道德规范
for whom the ethical guidelines on solicitation
实际上就是为老年人而制定的
were virtually created by the ABA.
查克  我确定...
Chuck, I'm sure that --
吉米  如果你能解释明白
Jimmy, if you could clear this up,
会大有帮助
that would be helpful.
我去了阿马里洛探访一位客户
I went to Amarillo to confer with a client
确保我们在当地的案子
and to make sure that we had a solid,
建立在真诚可靠的基础上
good-faith basis for our case there, overall.
如你们所知
And as many of you are aware,
我拜访了比计划多得多的养老院
I've visited more than my share of retirement homes.
他们可是关系紧密的社群
These are close-knit communities.
消息传播得总是特别快
Let me tell you, word gets around real fast.
住二期的桃乐茜买了辆新的电动车
If Dorothy in Phase Two gets a new Rascal Scooter,
马上大家就知道了
well, it's big news.
所以其他二十三位老年人主动找到你
So these other 23 residents, they approached you.
克利福德  在我踏进德州前
Cliff, they heard the scuttlebutt
他们早已听到了风声
before I crossed state lines.
我更没有必要挨家挨户拜访
And I certainly didn't have to go knocking on any doors.
他们都很想和一位带来好消息
And is it any surprise that they want to speak
说他们有钱拿的人谈话
with the guy who was there to show them
这有什么好惊讶的吗
they may have money coming their way?
我得说  这么一想
I gotta tell you, with all that in mind,
我还可以做得更好
I should've done better.
有道理  霍华德
Makes sense. Howard?
查克
Chuck?
我们能继续了吗
We good to move on?
查克这也不是顺带一提
And, Chuck, not incidentally,
我们必须十分谨慎  这至关重要
it is absolutely vital that we dot our I's and cross our T's here.
谢谢你宝贵的意见
Invaluable. So, thank you.
完美的代价乃永恒的警惕
The price of excellence is eternal vigilance.
没错
Indeed.
协调
Coordination.
我们刚刚是谈到这里吧
I believe that's where we left off.
没错
That's right.
布莱恩  你负责这个  你来说吧
Brian, this is your thing, so why don't you take this?
好吧
Sure.
考虑到这些案子所涉及的方面
Considering the dimensions of these cases,
进行具体分析和综合考量后
taken together and individually,
应该指定专人进行规划安排
it makes sense to designate someone to handle the scheduling.
我建议在戴维斯梅因成立一个小组
What I'm proposing is that we create a small team at D&M
专门负责协调单个诉讼及其之间的
dedicated specifically to coordinating all elements
所有因素
of the individual actions.
我们凡事都会告知哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
We'll loop in HHM on anything --
布莱恩  抱歉
Uh, Brian, I'm sorry.
抱歉打断你一下
Excuse me for interrupting.
我只是想说我同意查克的观点
Uh, I just want to say that I take Chuck's point.
真的
I do.
就像凯撒之妻一样
I mean, this is, like, a wife-of-Caesar type of thing.
意即不能受到别人的怀疑
连教唆的意思都不能有
There can't even be a hint of solicitation.
所以我准备不这么办了
So I'm gonna pull back.
好吧  不到矶鹞渡搞什么见面会了
All right, no more meet-and-greets at the Sandpiper facilities.
我会另想办法的
I'll find another way to proceed.
吉米  这我们就交给你了
Well, Jimmy, we'll leave that up to you.
联系客户是你负责的事
You know, client outreach is your department.
说到哪儿了来着
Uh, where was I?
对
Okay, right.
如果我们能在新墨西哥有更稳固的指挥中心
If we have a more consolidated nerve center here in New Mexico,
就能...
where the...
金  我该上哪儿搞尼德曼的供词
Hey, Kim, uh, where can I get a copy of that Neiderman deposition?
我有一份多的  吉米
I've got an extra Neiderman, Jimmy.
给你一份吧
You can have one of mine.
谢了  艾琳
Oh, wow. Thanks, Erin.
不客气
Yeah, no worries.
该死  我放哪儿了
Shoot. Where'd I put that?
谢了...
Thanks, that's...
查克真是令人难以置信
Man, do you believe Chuck in there?
天啊  还教唆
Jesus. Solicitation?
我告诉你  我们当初拼命立案的时候
Let me tell you, when we were building this case,
我可是追在逛商场的八十岁老头后面
I was chasing down 80-year-old mall walkers.
这才叫教唆
That was solicitation.
但他有说我什么吗
But did he say "Boo"?
当然没有
Bullshit he did.
你在德州做了什么
What happened in Texas?
没什么
Nothing.
我做了我该做的
I did my job.
你没有在休息室里给那些老家伙载歌载舞吗
You didn't do a song and dance in the dayroom for the old-timers?
没有  没有
No. No.
没...没在休息室里
Not -- not in the dayroom.
吉米  教唆他人会让你被取消律师资格的
Jimmy, you know solicitation can get you disbarred.
这点很重要
This matters.
我认为最重要的是
Well, here's what I think matters --
现在二十四名老年人有自己的代表了
24 senior citizens now have representation.
我去之前
Before I went,
他们根本不知道自己被剥削了
they didn't even know they were getting ripped off.
现在他们有我们撑腰
Now they have us in their corner.
这怎么能不算一种胜利呢
How is that not a win?
你刚刚说你会另想办法
You said in there you'd find another way.
你是认真的吗
Did you mean it?
当然了  绝对的  我...
Sure. Absolutely. I --
听着  我...
Look, I...
我要告诉你一件非常重要的事
I need you to understand something very critical here.
说吧
Shoot.
为了给你弄到这份工作  我拿我的饭碗作担保
I put myself on the line to get you this job.
好吧
Uh, okay.
我还以为是因为我擅长与老人打交道呢
I thought it was 'cause I'm sensational with old people.
那你以为是谁告诉他们的
Yeah, and who do you think told them that?
所以呢...这算是你帮了我吗
So, what -- you threw me a bone?
不...混蛋
No...asshole.
你知道我相信你
You know I believe in you.
后来我也说服他们相信你
But then I made my beliefs known to them.
现在你做的一切在霍华德看来就代表着我
And now everything you do reflects back on me with Howard,
因为说到底  是我说服他冒险让你试一试
'cause ultimately, I talked him into going out on a limb for you, too.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
是...是我的承诺  是我的判断
It's -- it's -- it's my word, it's my judgment.
明白
Yeah.
你我都知道你能胜任这份工作
You and I both know you can do this job.
但拜托你用正确的方式
But please, you just have to do it right.
你得确保
Well... you want to make sure
电池的方向正确  不然没有用
you put in the batteries the right way or he won't work.
然后合上盖子
Then you close them up.
然后...
And...
我觉得...我觉得这样就行了  小姑娘
I think -- I think you're good to go, young lady.
你捏一下它的脚试试
Why don't you give his foot a squeeze?
它真好笑
He's funny!
亲爱的
Oh, darlin'.
我就叫你...哼哼先生吧
I think I'll name you... Mr. Snuggles.
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
我去给你拿点土豆泥
I'm gonna get you some mashed potatoes.
这些钱应该够你撑过下个月了
That should get you through to next month.
麦克  谢谢
Mike, thank you.
但你其实没必要...
But you shouldn't feel that you need to --
太迟了
Too late.
出什么事了
Something up?
感觉好像有什么事
Feels like something's up.
不  只是...
No, it's...
我睡得不够
I didn't get much sleep.
-我的头...  -抱歉
- My head's... - I'm sorry.
跟我说这不关我的事  那我就不管了
You tell me it's none of my business, I'll drop it.
我不想让你担心
I don't want you to worry.
我也不喜欢担心
Not the worrying kind.
前两晚  我听到了枪声
Last two nights, I heard gunshots.
第一晚  可能在一两个街区外
First night, they were maybe a block or two over
我惊醒了
and woke me up.
我第一反应是鞭炮声
My first thought was firecrackers,
我当时这么认为的
and that's what I assumed at the time,
但是昨晚  我绝对没听错
but then last night -- there's no mistaking it.
一共三声
There was three of them.
很快  "啪啪啪"三声  更近了
They were quick -- pop, pop, pop -- closer.
好像...
It was...
他们就在房子外面
like they were right outside the house.
你报警了吗
You call the cops?
报了
Yeah.
警察一小时后才过来
Took them over an hour to get here,
在周围看了整整两分钟
then they looked around for a whole two minutes,
当然没什么发现
but by then, of course, there was nothing to see.
我今晚待这儿
I'm staying here tonight.
不用  麦克
No, Mike, no.
-没这个必要  -我没问题
- That's not necessary. - No, it is not a problem.
我睡沙发
I'll take the couch.
麦克  你问了我才回答
Mike, you asked, so...I answered.
别让我后悔告诉你
Please don't make me sorry I told you.
凯莉  过来
Kaylee, come, hmm?
吃晚饭
Get your supper.
那科泉市呢
What about Colorado Springs?
283个居住者  发了283封信函
283 residents, and we sent out 283 mailers.
行  那有多少回函呢
Yeah, and how many response cards came back?
零
Zero.
零吗
Zero?
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
达纳  托尼  再见
Dana, Toni, have a good one.
再见  梅因先生
Bye, Mr. Main.
You, too, Mr. Main.
克利福德  能谈会儿吗
Cliff, uh, could I have a second?
怎么了
What's up?
是寄给矶鹞渡信函的事
Uh, yeah, it's the Sandpiper mailers.
我们应该有约百分之十二到十五的回信
Yeah, we should be getting responses of like 12 to 15 percent,
但只有一两个点
but we're getting ones and twos.
科泉市甚至为零
In Colorado Springs, zero.
怎么会这样
Wow. How can that be?
他们员工搞的鬼吧
I'm thinking it's the staff.
信封交给居住者前就被员工扔了吧
They're tossing the mailers before they can reach the residents.
可能是他们上级要他们这么做的
Maybe they got told to do it by the Sandpiper front office,
真可以以这个起诉他们
which would be actionable as hell.
前提是我们能证明  但很难证明
If we could prove it. Big "if."
我需要更多人力才做得到
And to do so would take more manpower than I can spare.
我们现在先继续争取更多委托人
For now, let's just stick with getting those client numbers up.
你最好另寻他法
Guess you better think of another way.
已经想好了
I think I got it.
电视广告  更具针对性
TV commercial. Highly targeted.
告诉你  在矶鹞渡里一切都很准时
Let me tell you, at Sandpiper, the trains run on time.
墨索里尼会很骄傲
Mussolini would be proud.
将意大利塑造成整齐划一和严密控制社会的法西斯领袖
我至今拜访的每个人日程都完全相同
Every one I visited so far, same exact schedule.
上午十点  水中有氧操
10:00 A.M., water aerobics.
下午两点  队列舞
2:00 P.M., line dancing.
诸如此类
So on and so forth.
下午三点到四点都是自由活动
They always leave 3:00 P.M. to 4:00 P.M. free.
为什么  因为要看《女作家与谋杀案》[美剧]
Why? "Murder, She Wrote."
这剧长盛不衰
It's been in syndication since like the 1850s,
跟你说  只要电视里一开始演
and let me tell you, when that thing comes on,
那些老年人就像飞蛾扑捕虫灯一样
it draws the blue-hairs like moths to a bug zapper.
下午三点十四  第一段以悬念结束
3:14 P.M., end of the first-act cliffhanger,
进第一个广告  戴维斯梅因律所
first commercial up, Davis & Main.
保证赚足眼球
Guaranteed eyeballs -- lots of 'em.
矶鹞渡对此无能为力
There's nothing Sandpiper can do about that.
我们几年前做过一个广告
We ran a commercial a few years back --
也是起集体诉讼案
another class-action case.
对我们算是新鲜玩意儿
Kind of a new thing for us.
我不习惯这么做
Now, it's not exactly my go-to,
但我持开放态度
but generally speaking, I'm open to it.
我们下周再谈
We will talk next week.
真棒
Great.
一路平安
Safe travels.
朱利安出品
客户  戴维斯梅因律所
"间皮瘤"
如果你或你的家人被确诊患有
If you or a family member have been diagnosed
间皮瘤或相关疾病
with mesothelioma or related conditions,
你可获得经济赔偿
you may be entitled to monetary damages.
间皮瘤是一种罕见肺病
Mesothelioma is a rare lung disease,
通常因接触石棉患病
usually associated with exposure to asbestos,
石棉是已知致癌物
a known human carcinogen.
长期吸入石棉纤维
Long-term inhalation of asbestos fibers
会导致严重甚至致死疾病
can cause serious or fatal illnesses,
包括恶性肺癌
including malignant lung cancer,
间皮瘤和石棉肺
mesothelioma, and asbestosis.
我记得他们很努力才弄好那个
Remember they worked real hard to get that just right.
弄好什么
To get what just right?
波纹效果
Oh, the -- the swirl.
他们想做得朦胧些  但又不要太朦胧
They wanted it kind of nebulous, but not too nebulous.
还有速度的问题
Then there was the issue of the speed.
我记得他们为此开了很多会
I remember there were a lot of meetings about that.
...受害者和他们的家人
...victims and their families.
-我想是吧  -免费咨询
- I'll bet. - For your free consultation,
请拨打戴维斯梅因律所505-242-7700
call Davis & Main at 505-242-7700.
505-242-7700
That's 505-242-7700.
克利福德同意拍这玩意儿吗
Cliff signed off on this?
合伙人非常高兴
The partners were very happy.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得...
I think...
这算哪门子广告  演技呢
whatever happened to showmanship?
看过来
Yo, check it out.
利口乐
Ricola!
你们两个混蛋小丑能专业点吗
Will you two ass clowns act like the professionals
要对得起你们父母为你们花的钱
your parents are paying for you to become?
这东西很贵的
This happens to be very valuable.
是吗  这是什么
Yeah? What is it?
这个是阿尔卑斯牧童
This one is, uh, the Alpine Shepherd Boy.
送给她侄子的
It's for her nephew.
来  跟我来
So, come -- join me.
制片会议  开始吧
Production meeting -- bring it in.
好
All right.
听着  团队合作实现梦想
Now, look, teamwork makes the dream work.
我们同心协力  就能够
Together, we can make something --
可以这么说  共谱华美乐章
dare I say it? -- bravura.
这是千载难逢的良机
And this is a golden opportunity,
尤其是对你俩来说
especially for you guys,
因为会在整个西南部播出
'cause it's gonna play all around the Southwest,
谁知道这会带来什么呢
so who knows what it could lead to?
最好能给我们每人带来一百块
It better lead to a hundred bucks each.
你要钱做什么
What is it with you and money?
存起来买VX2000摄像机
Saving up for a VX2000.
问你们个问题
Hey, pop quiz --
我们三个与韦尔斯  费里尼和伯格曼
what do we three have in common with the greats --
三人均为著名导演
这样的伟大人物有什么共同点
Welles, Fellini, Bergman -- the biggies?
什么
What?
他们三人  无一例外
All three of them -- to a man --
都曾在利润丰厚
worked in the highly lucrative,
凭创意获取回报的广告业工作过
creatively rewarding field of advertising,
而今晚  我们就要跟随他们的脚步
and tonight, we join them.
真让人兴奋  对吧
This is heady stuff, right?
那么  听好了
Okay. So, pay attention.
画面从老奶奶开始  她坐在摇椅上摇
We open on granny, and she is rocking.
就这样来回地摇
So she's back and forth,
慢慢地摇啊摇
just very back...and forth.
然后  非常缓慢且平稳地
And then, very slowly and smoothly,
摄影机移向她的...
the camera, uh... moves towards her...
-移动摄影车吗  -移动摄影车  没错
- Dolly? - A dolly -- good.
你看这有移动摄影车吗
See a dolly here?
你们没带移动摄影车来
You guys didn't bring a dolly?
没有
Nope, no dolly.
你没说要带移动摄影车来
You didn't ask for a dolly.
-得提前说  摄影车要额外收费  -是的
- Gotta ask, dude. Dolly's extra. - It's true.
好吧  那就没有吧
Okay, no dolly.
那我们就即兴发挥一下
We will improvise, then.
顺着我的思路
Stay with me.
她摇晃着
She's rocking.
打着寒战
She's shivering.
紧紧抓着一个破旧的披肩
She's clutching at a tattered shawl.
那些混蛋把她的暖气停掉了
They turned the heat off on her, these evil bastards.
她又冷又饿  孤单一人
She's cold and hungry, she's friendless.
真是一幅令人心痛的画面
This is heart-rending stuff, man.
一个长镜头  用黑白色调
Okay, it's a oner, and it's shot in glorious black and white.
这个可以做到吧
We can do that, right?
可以
Yeah.
就这样而已吗
So that's it?
老太太坐在椅子上
Old lady in a chair?
这就是你的广告
That's your commercial?
你这副样子有人喜欢吗
Does anybody like you?
我准备好拍特写了  麦吉尔先生
I'm ready for my close-up, Mr. McGill.
一记高飞球  稍偏离正中
...And an easy, easy pop fly off dead center.
墨菲在之前的八场比赛中29击13中
Murphy's gone 13 for 29 over his last 8 games,
安打率为0.343  非常棒
batting a blistering 343 overall,
刘易斯现在又在跟教练商量
and now Lewis again working quickly with the bench.
墨菲投球  球触地两次进入人群
Murphy swings, it's a two-hopper into the crowd.
界外球
Foul ball.
祝你今天愉快
Have a good one.
出什么事了
Hey, honey. What's happening?
怎么了
What's wrong?
发生什么了
What happened?
凯莉呢
Where's Kaylee?
她没事  在学校  她还不知道
She's at school. She's fine. She doesn't know about it.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
我指给你看
Let me show you.
那上面
It's up -- it's up there.
你看到了吗
You see it?
就在那上面
It's right up there.
看到了吗  你看到它的形状了吗
You see that? You see the shape of it?
你看到了吧
You do see it, right?
看到了
I-I see it.
你什么时候听到的枪声
What time did you hear the shots?
凌晨两点十三分
2:13 this morning.
我当时看了钟  一共有三声
I looked at the clock. It was three of them.
跟上次一模一样
It was exactly like last time.
你也没有报警  报了吗
And you didn't call the police. Or did you?
没有  报警有什么用
No, I... What's the point?
我在想有没有其他的可能...
I'm thinking outside the box, but...
有没有可能是你做梦梦到的
you think maybe it's possible that you dreamed it?
有时会发生这种情况
It happens sometimes.
我没有做梦  麦克
I didn't dream it, Mike.
因为我昨晚一夜没合眼
Because I didn't sleep a wink last night.
这就是子弹的痕迹  肯定是
That came from a bullet. I mean, it must have.
昨晚之前还没有
It wasn't there before last night.
我跟你保证  我不知道...
I promise you that, and I don't know --
好了
Okay.
-好了  -天啊
- Okay. - Jesus...
我就在这里
I mean, I was here.
我一直在这里  而你不在
I was here, and you weren't.
我相信你
I believe you.
好吧
All right.
那你和凯莉要离开这栋房子
That's it. We're getting you and Kaylee out of this house.
就这么定了
End of story.
你对这些东西不好奇吗
You ever wonder about these things?
什么东西
What things?
这个  为什么会有这些东西
This. Like, what's the story with these?
是谁第一个说
Who was it who first said,
"我知道了  就放一大碗球吧"
"Hey, I know -- big bowl of balls."
我不知道
I don't know.
房子自带的
They came with the place.
要你说
No shit.
世界上每间公司临租房里都有这东西
They're in every corporate apartment in the world.
就像基甸国际赠送的《圣经》
They're like the Gideon Bible.
好啦  不要嫉妒我的一大碗球了
Hey, don't be jealous of my big bowl of balls.
别丢人了
It's unbecoming.
为什么一定要摆空花瓶呢
Why do they all have to have empty vases?
法律规定的  这是比喻的说法
Well, it's the law. Plus, it's a metaphor.
我必须得说
I got to say,
我会想念美甲店的振动按摩椅的
I will miss the Nail Salon's vibrating chairs.
为了你
Well, for you,
我可以让这的任何椅子都振动起来
I can make any chair in this place vibrate.
准备好了吗
You ready for this?
好的  开始播放
Kay. Here goes.
你现在八十六岁
You're 86 years old.
是科泉市矶鹞渡生活协助中心的住户
You're a resident of Sandpiper, Colorado Springs.
你刚刚吃完你的午茶点心  酸橙果冻
You just finished your afternoon snack, lime Jell-O.
酸橙  了解
Lime, got it.
你正在休息室
You're in the dayroom,
看你最爱看的电视剧
you're watching your favorite TV program.
出什么事了呢
What's this?
卡伯特湾又发生了一桩谋杀案吗
There's been another murder in Cabot Cove?
不会吧
No!
没错  警长无能为力
Yes. The sheriff is in over his head,
杰西卡·弗莱彻不得不再次
and once again, Jessica Fletcher has to put aside the novel
把她在写的小说放一边来协助执法
she's been writing and assist law enforcement.
令人震惊的是
Shocker!
凶手留下一封密文  然后进广告
The killer left behind a cryptogram -- and commercial.
新墨西哥大学  媒体实验室出品
戴维斯梅因律所
《是谁偷走了你的养老金》
我丈夫和我节衣缩食过了很多年
My husband and I scrimped and saved for so many years.
为了不成为家庭的负担
We did our best to build a nest egg
我们尽力攒下了一笔养老金
so that we wouldn't be a burden to our family.
罗纳德去世后  我搬进了一家生活协助中心
After Ronald passed, I moved to an assisted-living facility --
很不错的地方
a nice place.
他们说会照顾好一切
They told me they'd take care of everything,
但有一天  他们说我一分钱都没有了
but then, one day, they said all my money was gone.
怎么会这样
How could that be?
钱都去哪儿了
Where did it all go?
她装哭的是吧
That's not a real tear, is it?
-如果你或是爱人...  -是眼药水
- If you or a loved one... - It's Visine.
...是矶鹞渡生活协助中心
...is a resident of a Sandpiper Crossing facility
或是其他有关退休社区的居民
or other associated retirement community,
你也许有资格获得补偿
you may be eligible to receive compensation.
如需免费咨询
For a free consultation,
请致电戴维斯梅因律所
call the law offices of Davis & Main
电话505-242-7700
at 505-242-7700.
That's 505-242-7700.
怎么样
Well?
你拍的吗
You made that?
和一些电影专业学生做的吗
With... some film students?
我导的
I directed.
看起来  很专业
It looks... professional.
还有呢
And?
如果我是一个八十六岁的矶鹞渡居民
And if I were an 86-year-old Sandpiper resident...
我会打过去
I'd be dialing.
太棒了
Yes.
击掌
Up top.
而且一切都遵守了
And all made in accordance with the rules and regulations
美国律师协会的规章制度
of the American Bar Association.
很好
Good.
真不敢相信戴维斯梅因会支持你
I can't believe Davis & Main went for it.
那么
Well...
我现在主管客户联系
I'm in charge of the department.
是啊  但克利福德居然没有异议
Yeah, but still, you know, Cliff Main was fine with this.
他为什么会有
Why wouldn't he be?
不  我是说这太棒了
No, it's -- it's fantastic.
庆祝一下吧
Let's celebrate.
我要加点酒  你要吗
I'm getting more wine. You want some?
还用问
Absolutely.
《戴维斯梅因律所  是谁偷走了你的养老金》
非常好  谢谢
Very good. Thank you.
科罗拉多州科泉市
Colorado Springs, Colorado.
我想要KKTV11频道的号码
Yeah, I'd like the number for KKTV, channel 11.
奥马尔  联邦快递什么时候下班
Omar, what's the cutoff for FedEx?
我要寄个包裹  十万火急
I need to get a package out, tout suite.
是的  能帮我接通你们的广告销售部吗
Uh, yes, can you connect me to your ad sales department?
多谢
Thanks.
牙床没问题  没有老化
Gums look good, no recession.
舌头也没问题
Tongue looks good, too.
眼睛不浑浊
Eyes are clear.
这个小美女身体很好
This little lady's in fine fettle.
如果需要  我可以叫人修剪一下它的指甲
We can have one of the girls trim her nails, if you like.
不用了  改天吧
No, some other time.
有什么工作吗
What do you got for me?
保镖  两百块
Bodyguard job, 200 bucks.
还有吗
What else?
这是我这儿最适合你的了
For you, that's the best fit I've got.
我认识一个放高利贷的
I know a loan shark.
一直需要人去帮他收账
Always needs enforcement and recovery.
报酬不错而且稳定
Pays good, and it's steady work.
大多数时间只是放放狠话
Most of the time, we're just talking intimidation, strictly verbal.
"大多数时间"
"Most of the time."
我才不要当打手
I'm not breaking legs.
还有吗
What else?
听着  我们讨论过
Look, we discussed this.
你想多赚点  就要做相应的工作
You want next-level pay, you got to do next-level work.
我尊重你的原则
I respect where you're coming from on this thing.
真的
I do.
但事情就是这么办的
But that's just how it goes.
好了
All right.
它要打六个月疫苗
She's gonna need a DHPP shot, six months.
我们会给你发提醒卡的
We'll send you a reminder card.
到时再说吧
Till then.
给我保镖的工作
Give me the bodyguard job.
两百块行吗
For $200?
时间地点打电话告诉你
Call you with the where and the when.
大家都知道...
So, everybody knows --
都知道了
They know.
所有以7700开头的电话线路
Every line starting with 7700
都已经转到等候区还有你的办公室
has been rerouted to the bullpen, plus your office.
所有助理都会保持线路畅通
All the assistants know to keep them open.
如果你在打电话时另一通电话进来
So, if you're on a call and another call comes in,
电话不会被转到答录机对吗
the call doesn't go to an answering machine, right?
因为  这非常重要
Because -- very important --
老年人不喜欢和机器人说话
old people don't like talking to robots.
如果我在打电话  另一通电话进来
If I'm on a call and another call comes in,
会转给梅达
it'll roll over to Maida.
然后艾里斯会接下一个
After that, Iris will get the next one,
再然后朱利安  然后芭芭拉
then Julian, and then Barbara,
还有伊冯  一个接一个下去
and Yvonne, right on down the line.
好极了
Good.
那就这样
Let's make that the plan, then.
那么...
Oh, so --
你的表几点了
What time do you have?
过一刻了
Uh, quarter after.
广告应该在播了对吧
It should be running now, right?
还有什么事吗
Is there... anything else?
没了  谢谢
No. Thanks.
我会在办公室的
It's...I'll just... be in my office.
快来电话啊
Come on.
快打快打  科泉市的电话  快来啊
Come on. Come on, Colorado Springs, come on.
下午好  戴维斯梅因律师事务所
Good afternoon, Davis & Main, attorneys at law.
有什么能为您效劳的
How may I help you?
是的  女士  是的  真是太不幸了
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am, that is unfortunate.
立案需要您先留一下姓名
Now, to get your case started, may I ask for a name
以及电话号码  方便我们的律师联系您
and the number for one of our attorneys to reach you?
下午好  戴维斯梅因律师事务所
Good afternoon. Davis & Main, attorneys at law.
有什么能为您效劳的
How can I help you?
是的  没错
Yes, that is correct.
下午好  戴维斯梅因律师事务所
Good afternoon, Davis & Main, attorneys at law.
Good afternoon, Davis & Main.
这里是矶鹞渡热线
Sandpiper hotline.
有什么能为您效劳的
How can I help you?
我们稍后再联系您
We'll get back to you.
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我们马上把相关材料寄给您
We'll be happy to send an information packet right out to you.
请问您目前居住在
May I ask, are you currently a resident
矶鹞渡生活协助中心吗
of a Sandpiper Crossing facility?
下午好  戴维斯梅因律师事务所
Good afternoon. Davis & Main.
Good afternoon. Davis & Main, attorneys at law.
漂亮
Bingo.
什么事
Yeah.
今晚来了一个活
Something came in this evening,
报酬绝对高
and it's definitely next-level pay.
是吗
Yeah?
不过你这么挑剔  估计又不肯接吧
It's probably a long shot, given your selectivity.
什么活
What's the job?
我问了  那人不肯说
I asked. Guy wouldn't tell me.
不过不管是什么活  酬劳很可观
But whatever it is, it's serious money.
而且那人
And the guy...
指名要你
he specifically asked for you.
那人是谁
And who's the guy?
我控制不住了  长官
I can't hold it, sir.
失控了  上校
No control on the planes, Captain.
我们正在快速下沉
We're going down and fast.
"我们正在快速下沉"
"We're going down and fast."
快看
Check this out.
这地方很精彩
This is a good part.
他们最后全死光了吗  告诉我这个就行
So, do they all die? Tell me that much.
洛克·哈德森带他们撞冰山了吗
Does Rock Hudson run 'em into an iceberg?
他先拍的这个还是《麦克米兰夫妇》
Is this...before or after he did "McMillan & Wife"?
别说话  好好看
Shut up. Watch the movie.
你怎么会有这么奇怪的爱好
What is this weird fascination you have
喜欢看人被困在北极
with stories of men trapped on the North Pole?
《大北极》的设定在北极
"Ice Station Zebra" is on the North Pole.
《怪形》发生在南极
"The Thing" takes place on the South Pole.
这两个天差地别
They literally could not be any more different.
我爸特喜欢这个
My dad loves this one.
是啊  他和霍华德·休斯都爱看
Yeah, him and Howard Hughes.
是啊
I know, right?
都对这片子赞不绝口
Can't get two finer reviews than that.
空气瓶组内还剩多少压力
How much pressure's left in the air banks?
不足八百磅  长官
Down 800 pounds, sir.
是老板
It's the boss.
这时候打电话来
At this hour?
是啊
Yeah.
祝贺嘛  多晚都不嫌迟
It's never too late for congratulations.
克利福徳  天哪  这个点了你还在办公室
Cliff, Jesus, you're still at the office?
你播了一支广告
You ran a commercial?
是啊  天哪
Yeah, and, oh, my God,
我跟你说  那反响简直
let me tell you, the response has been --
你拍了一个广告  没给我过目就播出去了
You ran a commercial without ever showing it to me,
也没有事先征求我和合伙人的意见
without first consulting me and my partners.
你真以为我会同意吗
Did you actually think that was gonna fly?!
我打算明天早上告诉你的
I was planning on telling you in the morning.
广告播出一天之后才告诉我
The day after it aired?!
只播出了一次  只面向很小一部分观众
I only ran it once, just in one small market.
只是个试验而已  好吧
It was kind of an experiment, all right?
没什么人注意
Kind of under the radar.
而且公平地讲
And in all fairness,
你说过的  客户联系这块归我管
you did tell me client outreach was my department.
不要狡辩了
Don't be disingenuous.
这个广告提到我的公司名了吧
This commercial -- I take it my firm's name is mentioned?
是的  提到了
Yes. Yeah.
天哪
Jesus...
霍华德说你有些古怪
Howard said you were a little eccentric.
他可没说你这么能惹事儿
He didn't tell me you were a goddamn arsonist!
克利福德  说真的  我不认为
Cliff, to be fair, I don't think, uh...
如果是我误解了你的话
I apologize if there was any misreading
我道歉
of the situation on my part,
但是现在形势大好
but there's a very positive headline here.
我们今天接到了103个电话
We got 103 phone calls today,
区区七百块广告费就有这么好的效果
off a measly $700 ad buy.
这种投资回报率可不是你...
Now that kind of return on investment you can't g--
明早八点  到我办公室来  合伙人也在
Tomorrow morning, 8:00, my office, with the partners,
把你拍的那玩意儿也带来
and we want to see this thing.
克利福德  等你看到这广告  你肯定
Cliff, when you see this, I know you'll --
好的  克利福德
Yeah, Cliff.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也是
Yeah, you, too.
好的
Okay.
再见
See ya.
成功男人啊
Golden boy.
说的就是我
That's me.
我错过什么了
So, what'd I miss?
炸了没
Anything blow up yet?
觉得该小心行事了
Feeling cautious?
说吧  你把我叫来这里什么事
You gonna tell me what we're doing here?
我遇到麻烦了
I've got a problem.
-然后呢  -这个麻烦
- Okay. - This problem...
我自己解决不了
I can't solve it myself.
这个麻烦  是人还是事
This problem -- is it a who or a what?
有个人
There's a guy.
我想要他消失
I need him to go away.
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340